QUESTIONS = [
    {
        "question": "What is the hottest planet in the solar system? \n",
        "answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What has hands but cannot clap? \n",
        "answer": "A clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Sea of Tranquility? \n",
        "answer": "The Moon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What has a neck but no head? \n",
        "answer": "A bottle"
    },
    {
        "question": "what has a head and tail but no body? \n",
        "answer": "A coin"
    },
    {
        "question": "what fills a room but takes up no space? \n",
        "answer": "Light"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is a baker's dozen? \n",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many wives did King Henry VIII have beheaded? \n",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of Shakespeare's plays is known as the Scottish play? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "Macbeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whoever makes it, has no need of it. Whoever buys it, has no use for it. Whoever uses it, can neither feel nor see it. What is it? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "A coffin"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is the city of Nashville? \n",
        "answer": "Tennessee"
    },
     {
        "question": "In what year did Tony Blair become British Prime Minister? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "1997"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which British City is street artist Banksy closely associated with? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "Bristol"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which language has the most native speakers? \n",
        "answer": "Spanish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the last Tsar of Russia? \n",
        "answer": "Nicholas II"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main ingredient in guacamole? \n",
        "answer": "Avocado"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet has the most moons? \n",
        "answer": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many wisdom teeth does the average adult have? \n",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many lives is a cast said to have? \n",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest bone in the human body? \n",
        "answer": "Femur"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which nuts are used to make marzipan? \n",
        "answer": "Almonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of pastry are profiteroles made out of? \n",
        "answer": "Choux"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which musician won the Nobel Prize for literature in 2016? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bj√∂rn Again is a tribute band for which world-famous pop group? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "ABBA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What spirit is mixed with ginger beer in a Moscow mule? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "Vodka"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many humps does a Bactrian camel have? \n",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a female deer known as? \n",
        "answer": "A doe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the music producer commonly referred to as The Fifth Beatle? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "George Martin"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which UK city was Cadbury founded? \n",
        "answer": "Birmingham"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who originally recorded the classic ballad I Will Always Love You in 1973? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "Dolly Parton"
    },
    {
        "question": "Constantinople and Byzantium are former names of which major city? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "Istanbul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has the most castles? \n",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main ingredient of black pudding?? \n",
        "answer": "Blood"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did the Chernobyl disaster occur? \n",
        "answer": "1986"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which British King suffered from a stammer, as portrayed by Colin Firth in The King's Speech? \n",  # noqa
        "answer": "George VI"
    },
]
